Guide to the Laurence MacDaniels papers, [ca. 1915]-1986.
Laurence MacDaniels papers,
- Nothern Nut Growers Association 1977-78 correspondence Jaynes, Lagerstadt, and others, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
- Northern Nut Growers Association returned questionnaires, 1969 (Box 31)
- Northern Nut Growers Association Testing 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
- Manuscript Readers Digest - nut culture, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Northern Nut Growers Association 1977 correspondence, 1977 (Box 31)
- Zimmerman - "Hybrids on the American Paw Paw", Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Organic gardening and farming, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Northern Nut Growers Association (Jaynes Chase) 1975, 1975 (Box 31)
- Northern Nut Growers Association general file, 1977 (Box 31)
  marked 1977, includes earlier correspondence
- Notebook Bougainvillea Project, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea project working folder 1970-72, 1970-1972 (Box 31)
  India catalogs
- Winter injury to Baldwin apples photos 1958, 1958 (Box 31)
- Photos and negatives stock - scion relationship, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Baileya December 1976, 1976-12 (Box 31)
- Hackett - Bougainvillea in San Diego, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Notebook - mostly bougainvillea and some others, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea Project 1965-73 correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea clone description working folder, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea older material 1965, 1965 (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea old nursery lists, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea start of project 1964, other older material, 1964 (Box 31)
- Manuscript Bougainvillea July 1979, 1979-07 (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea Project 1967, 1967 (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea manuscript reference and marked draft, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea photos and prints, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Letters Popenoe, Lawrence, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea working folder, 1969-1970 (Box 31)
  exchange lists, correspondence 1969-1970
- Bougainvillea variety descriptions, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea letters 1972-74, 1972-1974 (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea 1974 manuscript thorns, reference, 1974 (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea thorn, description blanks, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bougainvillea regarding publication by American Horticultural Society, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Lily slides, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Bougainvillea slides, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Bougainvillea, 1977-1979 (Box 32)
  correspondence regarding publication; 77-78 outline for paper; correspondence 1979; 1979 - next to last revision; manuscript rough copy; duplicate material; Baileya manuscript final revision 1979
- Clippings: environment, nuclear energy, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Cornell bulletins "Growing Vegetables Organically," "Facts About Organic Gardening," "Mixes for Commercial Plant Growing", Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Glens - published articles and clippings, manuscripts 15 years after logging, photos, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Letters to Ithaca Journal, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Original copy "Comments on the Energy Problem as Related to the Bell Nuclear Station", Date Unknown (Box 32)
- J.D. Kirkpatrick reprints 1960-64, 1960-1964 (Box 32)
- Goodell paper - "Woody Food Producing Plants", Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Near East Foundation - 1944-45 correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 32)
- United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration 1944-45 correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 32)
- Correspondence 1944-45, 1944-1945 (Box 32)
- Paw paws seeds Australia, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- To be filed 1976-1981, 1976-1981 (Box 32)
- Rose Garden - letters, nut photos, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Material from Audrey O'Connor (conservation planning), Date Unknown (Box 32)
- McGraw Hill revision walnuts for encyclopedia 1980, 1980 (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous material - Cornell articles, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Tree crops - drafts (2 folders), Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Brian Caldwell tree crops proposal, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Bio Science, Date Unknown (Box 32)
  correspondence regarding publication tree crops
- Comparative study ploem Zahur, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- South Pacific material including photos, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Horticulture in the Philippines terminal report (marked copy), Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Soil Tests, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Draft statement before New York State Conservation Committee 1970, 1970 (Box 32)
- General nut correspondence 1966, 1966 (Box 32)
- Correspondence 1977, 1977 (Box 32)
- Plantations 1966, 1966 (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous 1966, 1966 (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous, bits, notes, etc., Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Undated notes, mostly Bougainvillea, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Correspondence, 1974-11 (Box 32)
  regarding article on nut tree propagation in Horticulture November 1974
- 1981 manuscript "80 years with Walnut", 1981 (Box 32)
- Waltox material 1976-1980, 1976-1980 (Box 32)
- April 1983 seminar - Education Department, 1983-04 (Box 32)
- Waltox 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 32)
- Waltox - correspondence, references 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 32)
- Waltox - earthworms, compost 1977, 1977 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1977 (important material), 1977 (Box 32)
- Waltox - Times article 1977 (correspondence, drafts), 1977 (Box 32)
- Waltox - Horticulture magazine 1977, 1977 (Box 32)
- Waltox - 1978 growing season, 1978 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1977-1978, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1978, 1978 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1979, 1979 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1980 tomatoes, 1980 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1980 potatoes, 1980 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1980; 1st rough draft, 1980 (Box 32)
- Waltox - manuscripts 1980, 1980 (Box 32)
- Waltox - notes 1981 (2 folders), 1981 (Box 32)
- Waltox - 1982 manuscript for Nothern Nut Growers Association, 1982 (Box 32)
- Waltox - 1983 effect on lilies, 1983 (Box 32)
- Waltox - 1984 correspondence, 1984 (Box 32)
- Waltox - turning over files to George Poppensiek, Cornell Veterinary College, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Waltox - slides, negatives, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Waltox photos, Date Unknown (Box 32)
- Waltox photos 1982, 1982 (Box 32)
- Glass enlarged microscope slides, Date Unknown (Box 33)
  unidentified as to date - perhaps master's thesis
- Thesis microscope slides, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Negatives anatomy text first edition, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Negatives and prints anatomy text 2nd edition, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Apple leaf paper 1943, negatives, extra prints, 1943 (Box 33)
- Photos and negatives of nuts, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Photos and negatives of lilies, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- North American Lily Society - quarterly bulletins 1953-57, miscellany, 1953-1957 (Box 33)
- North American Lily Society - 1961 (two folders), 1961 (Box 33)
- Lilies 1962 including judging, 1962 (Box 33)
- Lilies 1963 including judging, 1963 (Box 33)
- Handbook North American Lily Society judging and exhibiting lilies, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Appointment calendars 1950, 1951, 1950-1951 (Box 33)
- Correspondence, biographical material, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Correspondence Cornell gift (Plantations), Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Cornell - miscellaneous material, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- A.S. Eames Botanical Preserve, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- A.S. Eames Orchid Bog, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Natural areas, Date Unknown (Box 33)
- Manuscripts, Saturday Night Club, Rotary, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Yugoslavia correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Yugoslavia/Philippines, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Yugoslavia official correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Yugoslavia 1961 plant introduction (2 folders), 1961 (Box 34)
- Retirement, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Radio addresses 1930s, 1930 (Box 34)
- Plantations, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Botanical material, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Boynton interviews, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Chestnut saga manuscript, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Correspondence 1980, 1980 (Box 34)
- Conservation - general, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1980, 1980 (Box 34)
- Fluoridation, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Fertilizers, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Manuscripts Ithaca Journal "Destroying Life on Earth", Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Lily - history American Horticultural Society Lily Committee (very important material), Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Lily manuscripts with De Braff 1963, 1963 (Box 34)
- North American Lily Society Benlate study 1972-73 manuscripts and data, 1972-1973 (Box 34)
- 2nd lily project plans, data Terra Chlor Dexon 1972-76-77, 1972-1977 (Box 34)
- Lilies - Auratum study 1975, 1975 (Box 34)
- Lytell Cup, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- "Lily Disease Problems in North America" Synge Lily book manuscripts, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- George Slate lily, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Manuscripts of North American Lily Society history, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Lily Society source material, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Bulletins various lily societies, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Lily before 1980 - judging manuals, 1980 (Box 34)
- Lily correspondence before 1980, 1980 (Box 34)
- Lily disease paper with K. Horst manuscripts, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Northern Nut Growers Association general file 1975-77, 1975-1977 (Box 34)
- General nut before 1980 (Box 34)
- Newspaper clippings, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Oregon Bulb Farm, 1976-1977 (Box 34)
  mainly regarding G. Slate's lilies 1976-77
- Organic garden including manuscripts, talk before county agents, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Oberlin College, Date Unknown (Box 34)
- Political material including correspondence with Matt McHugh, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Tree crops up to 1979, 1979 (Box 35)
- Tree crops Davies, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- 1981 Seminar - Graduate School 70 years ago, 1981 (Box 35)
- Reprints, articles on fluorides, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Bioscience - Ehrlich scientist as social prophet, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- L.H. Bailey, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Articles, pictures (with negatives), Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Revised bilbiography 1981, 1981 (Box 35)
- Birds - changes in population, manuscripts 1984, 1984 (Box 35)
- Correspondence - Bougainvillea (after 1980), 1980 (Box 35)
- Bunch Disease Syndrome, 1982 (Box 35)
  correspondence, printed articles, 1982 draft article
- Circle Greenway - correspondence, publications, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- California Rare Fruit Growers - correspondence, publications, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Citizens Party, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Concern for the dying - correspondence, publications, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Compost pile - correspondence, publications, negatives, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Eames Bog - correspondence, photos, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Endangered species - notes on wild flower clones, 1981 manuscritps - approach to problem of endangered species, 1981 (Box 35)
- Environmental enhancement - other environmental publications, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Tompkins County Environmental Management Council, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Cornell Miscellany, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Coy Glen including 1979 LHM statement, 1979 (Box 35)
- Letter drafts 1983, 1983 (Box 35)
- Correspondence from March 1985-March 1986, 1985-03-1986-03 (Box 35)
- Fluoridation, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Talk - "Here we are, where do we go from here?", Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Correspondence - horticulture, walnut, paw paw, etc., Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Hospicare correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Hospicare legislation/correspondence relating to 1983, 1983 (Box 35)
- Hospicare source material, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Hospice related articles - "Die with Dignity," "When Does Life End?" - 21 May 1983 draft manuscripts, 1983 (Box 35)
- Correspondence in response to "When Does Life End?", Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Correspondence, articles, Richard Lamm, Governor of Colorado, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Lily - correspondence after 1980, 1980 (Box 35)
- Lily - Niel Stewart correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- North American Lily Society manuscript, correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- State representative Sam McNeil, correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- McGraw Hill correspondence - encyclopedia of science entry on walnuts, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- M.F. McHugh - U.S. Congress correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Memberships - correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Memorial Society, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- Correspondence - Richard Meister, Date Unknown (Box 35)
- General nut correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- General Northern Nut Growers Association correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Northern Nut Growers Association, Charles Burnham correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Northern Nut Growers Association, Spencer Chase correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Northern Nut Growers Association, Richard Jaynes correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Northern Nut Growers Association, 1981 research perspective, 1981 (Box 36)
- Nut culture - source material, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Nuclear material, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Oberlin Arboretum 1983, 1983 (Box 36)
- Orchids correspondence, publications, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Ornithology Lab, correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Paw paw material, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Paw paw correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Philosophy, correspondence, Peter Taverna, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Plantations - drafts of articles for bulletin, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Plantations, Coy Glen (draft to Ralph Barnard), Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Plantations - correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Political correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
  environment, nuclear war
- List of songs taped in Yugoslavia, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Tree crops - correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Tree crops - 1983 seminar, 1983 (Box 36)
- Tree crops - miscellaneous resources, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Tree crops - Davies (Leiberman), Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Black walnut toxicity, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- 1816 - "Froze to Death," other weather-related manuscripts, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- "What Price Wildlife?" - drafts, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Negatives logging, regeneration of glen articles, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- 1982 Waltox diary, 1982 (Box 36)
- Cytell Cup, Friend of the Land Award, correspondence; other miscellaneous correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Drafts, copies of articles - mainly environmental, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Waltox - lilies research 1983, 1983 (Box 36)
- Attention file, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Clippings 1983-85, 1983-1985 (Box 36)
- Tapes, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Conference December 17, 1982, 1982 (Box 36)
- Tree crops, Date Unknown (Box 36)
- Waltox 1 - 1981, 1981 (Box 36)
- Waltox 2 - 1981, 1981 (Box 36)
- Committee on Campus Trees, Date Unknown (Box 37)
- Greenbelt, Date Unknown (Box 37)
- North American Lily Society, Date Unknown (Box 37)
- Fluoridation, Date Unknown (Box 37)
- Fluoridation, Date Unknown (Box 38)
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 38)
- Lilies, Date Unknown (Box 38)
- Fluoridation, Date Unknown (Box 39)
- Lilies, Date Unknown (Box 39)
- Recollections, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Photographs and negatives, 1915-1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Accounts, 1917-1943 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Accounts, 1937-1938 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Accounts, 1946-1955 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Accounts, 1951-1965 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Accounts, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Accounts, 1957-1960 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Accounts, 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Accounts, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Accounts, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Accounts, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Accounts, 1970-1977 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Accounts, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Accounts, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Photographs: A. J. Heinicke, L. H. and Frances MacDaniels; Gamma Alpha, 804 E. State Street; Gamma Alpha picnics; Stubby Maynard; Wm. J. Robbins; white pine, Plantations, 1913-1915 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- (Slide) Canton Island, 1950 (?) (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
- (Slide) Fiji, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- (Slide) Garden: woodlot, magnolia, Lady Slippers, miscellaneous garden, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- (Slide) miscellaneous garden, Date Unknown (Box 41, Folder 5)
- (Slide) Hawaii: hula, Hawaii scenery, air flight, 1950(?) (Box 41, Folder 6)
- (Slide) Hawaii: general horticulture, 1950(?) (Box 41, Folder 7)
- (Slide) Ithaca: horticulture (flowers), 1975 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- (Slide) Lilies: March-August, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- (Slide) Lilies, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- (Slide) Lilies: West Virginia, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- (Slide) Lilies: Selected, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- (Slide) Lilies, 1956,1961 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- (Slide) Lilies: West Hill and misc., 1966 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- (Slide) Lilies: Lily show, etc., 1942-1957 (Box 41, Folder 15-16)
- (Slide) Lilies, 1942-1954 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- (Slide) Lilies: misc. hybrids, 1942-1953 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- (Slide) Lilies: slides for lecture, 1942-1961 (Box 41, Folder 19-21)
- (Slide) Lilies: West Hill, four frost lilies, frost damage, 1957-1965 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- (Slide) New Caledonia, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 23-25)
- (Slide) New Caledonia/New Hebrides: forest, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- (Slide) New Hebrides, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 27-28)
- (Slide) Nuts: walnut toxicity, frost crack, walnut pruning, 422 Chestnut Street snow, compost pile, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- (Slide) Nuts: Walnut toxicity, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 30-31)
- (Slide) Nuts: walnut toxicity slide for paper, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- (Slide) Nuts: walnut toxicity slides used in presentation paper, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- (Slide) Nuts: California walnuts, general cultivation,harvesting, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- (Slide) Nuts: California and Northwest misc., nuts, misc. Fruits, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- (Slide) Nuts: black line, stocks and deficiencies, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- (Slide) Nuts: graft unions, nut trees, Date Unknown (Box 41, Folder 37)
- (Slide) Nuts: pruning lecture, NNTA, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- (Slide) Nuts: frost damage, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- (Slide) Philippines coconuts, codong codong, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- (Slide) Philippines: fruits, nematodes, wilt, etc., apples, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- (Slide) Philippines: bananas, 1957-1958 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- (Slide) Pearson Young gardens, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- (Slide) Pink Lady Slippers, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- (Slide) Misc.: Pomology, orchard root study, Rhine River trip, 1964,1967 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- (Slide) Misc.: rubbish in glens, Yugoslavia, 1964(?), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 46)
- Lantern slide (4"x5"): Fei Valley, Taravano, Tahiti, 1927 (Box 41)
- Lantern slide (4"x5"): Azalea mallis, Date Unknown (Box 41)
- Environmental management file, 1976-1978 (Box 42)
- "Identify in folder Probably AE5" (1 print, 1 negative), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Apple trees (4 prints, 3 negatives), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Apple clusters (4 prints, 4 negatives), 1936 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous botanical (4 prints, 8 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 4)
- California, San Diego: tropical fruits (7 prints, 8 negatives), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- California, Coachella Valley: tropical fruits (8 prints, 7 negatives), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Course 121 slides (9 prints, 11 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Economic fruits (3 prints, 23 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Fiji (13 prints, 8 negatives), 1927 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Florida (1 print, 14 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Florida: botanical (17 prints, 4 negatives), 1921 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Florida: tropical fruits (15 prints, 10 negatives), 1921 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Fruit and orchard (46 prints), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Hawaii: miscellaneous botanical (18 prints, 6 negatives), 1927 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Ithaca: Plant Science Building Rhododendron in snow (3 prints, 4 negatives), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Ithaca: picnic: Pomology (Stewart Park?) (7 prints, negatives), 1936 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Ithaca: Cornell: Andrew D. White statue (postcard), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Lebanon (49 prints), 1944 (Box 43, Folder 18-19)
- Lily (7 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Maguay, [Mexico]: ferns (9 prints, 9 negatives), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Maguay, Mexico (13 prints, 7 negatives), 1921 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Mexico: palms, Horlorium (8 prints, 8 negatives), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Mexico: tropical fruits (2 prints, 3 negatives), 1921 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Nut shucking with auto hazel bushes (6 prints, 5 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Palms (2 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Philippines: Group outing Salac, J. Juan (6 prints, 14 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Philippines: Salac going away (9 prints, 5 negatives), 1936 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Philippines: Lildiran (?) wedding, Makiling folios (18 prints, 14 negatives), 1955 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Samoa: Miss Williams negatives (6 prints), 1927 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Tahitian: scenery, etc. (27 prints, 20 negatives), 1927 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Tonga (3 prints, 3 negatives), 1927 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Tropical [probably Mexico] (6 prints, 9 negatives), 1935 (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Tropical fruits (3 prints, 2 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Tropical and sub-tropical slides: vanilla (1 print, 1 negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Unidentified [Mexico?] ( prints, negatives), Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Note cards, Date Unknown (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Lebanon: 4 cans negative film, Date Unknown (Box 43)
- Pomology course material and index, 1925-1940 (Box 44)
- Correspondence concerning property in Mexico, 1939-1946 (Box 44)
- Notes and photographs related to collecting in Hawaii and Tahiti, 1926 (Box 44)
- Glass slides of Armenia, 1919-1920 (Box 45)
  Includes images of the Armenian genocide